<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>InnoCellence</title>
    <description>At InnoCellence, we are passionate about innovating the mobile, web, UX design, app development, and digital strategy solutions your business needs to succeed.</description>		
    <link>http://innocellence.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://innocellence.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />  
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>What Are the Advantages and Risks of Product Innovation — And How Can a Digital Innovation Consultant Help?</title>
        <link>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/19/advantages-risks-product-innovation.html</link>
        <dc:creator>InnoCellence Systems Pte. Ltd.</dc:creator>    
        <description>Product innovation isn’t an option in today’s business world – it’s a necessity. Long gone are the days when companies could rely on their flagship products, long product cycles, or traditional business models to sustain growth.

Now, companies must keep pace with the rapid changes in technology ...</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <guid>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/19/advantages-risks-product-innovation.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Your Business Needs a Mobile App</title>
        <link>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/18/3-reasons-why-your-business-needs-a-mobile-app.html</link>
        <dc:creator>InnoCellence Systems Pte. Ltd.</dc:creator>    
        <description>Mobile devices, like smartphones, have changed the way we communicate with friends and colleagues, the way we manage our social lives, and even the way we make purchases.

In fact, mobile devices have become so important to our daily lives, we carry them everywhere we go. Now, the whole world is ...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <guid>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/18/3-reasons-why-your-business-needs-a-mobile-app.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>7 Essential Social Listening Benefits Your Company Should Know About</title>
        <link>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/17/7-essential-social-listening-benefits.html</link>
        <dc:creator>InnoCellence Systems Pte. Ltd.</dc:creator>    
        <description>Social media has forever changed the way consumers talk about products, services, and brands. Now, all a customer needs to do to share good or bad product experience with 10 to 10,000+ of their “friends” is hit the “post” button on a social media account.

While the power of social media is worry...</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <guid>http://innocellence.com/d/en/feed/2015/11/17/7-essential-social-listening-benefits.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>娱乐至死｜今天你玩high了吗?</title>
        <link>http://innocellence.com/d/cn/feed/2015/10/14/are-you-getting-high-today.html</link>
        <dc:creator>Jiahang Song</dc:creator>    
        <description>伴随现今整个商业社会的发展，不止电视行业进入了全民娱乐的时代，和我们生活相关的各方各面都已经受到娱乐化的影响，从政治、宗教、媒体、体育一直到教育领域，悄无声息，乐此不彼。

比如你在星巴克买杯咖啡，付钱时掏出了积分卡；过几天麦当劳打广告“买套餐送Hello Kitty”促销活动；上淘宝收货，淘宝会告诉你“还差5次评论就可以升级”；买机票回家，东航有“天合联盟”积分，国航有“星空联盟”积分，等等。这些产品或服务中夹带的游戏化成分，其目的大都是为了留住消费者，增加粘度。
既然游戏化变成了各个商家跪舔的对象，那我们今天就来为大家来浅析一下游戏化到底是何方妖孽。

什么是游戏化？

大概每个人都...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <guid>http://innocellence.com/d/cn/feed/2015/10/14/are-you-getting-high-today.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
    
      <item>
        <title>布局社区医院，跨国药企数字化战略新玩法解析</title>
        <link>http://innocellence.com/d/cn/feed/2015/08/31/community-hospital-distribution.html</link>
        <dc:creator>Jian Zhu</dc:creator>    
        <description>1 背景介绍

1.1 新医改政策对社区基层的倾斜

东风吹，战鼓擂，国家新医改正在一步步落到实处。随着我国城镇化的快速推进、居民生活水平的提高、老龄化程度的加剧以及二胎政策的实施，大家对于医疗卫生服务的需求也日益增长。但由于我国医疗卫生资源总量不足，布局不均（优质资源全部集中在北上广深），加上卫生机构缺乏相对规范的分工协作机制（各自为政，太功利化），从而导致在目前的卫生服务体系下，群众“看病难，看病贵”的问题越来越突出（笔者作为80后在上有老下有小的情况下已经开始深有体会）。于是乎旨在优化医疗卫生资源、避免小病大治、减轻患者医疗负担以及提高整体医疗服务水平的新医改势在必行。

可以看到...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
        <guid>http://innocellence.com/d/cn/feed/2015/08/31/community-hospital-distribution.html</guid>
      </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>